<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Ben Adams&#39; Design Portfolio</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Ben Adams&#39; Design Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UI/UX Design &amp; Development for Biobanking App</title>
      <link>/portfolio/biobank-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/biobank-design/</guid>
      <description>Uncharted territory The biggest challenge of this project was that it was attempting to solve multiple, very complex problems, most of all the connecting of disparate data from various systems with their own formats.
Our team noticed early on the potential issues with an overly-complex application that was trying to do too much, and we convinced stakeholders to scale back the features in order to focus on the core of the application: Connecting disparate data Analyzing the connected data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Science Organization Redesign &amp; Style Guide</title>
      <link>/portfolio/earth-science-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/earth-science-redesign/</guid>
      <description>Simple but complex One of the biggest challenges of the project involved the website&#39;s audience. Because it catered to a wide range of users, from seasoned scientists, to college students, we had to find a way to make the content accessible, without watering it down.
So first, we needed to make sure that the content was arranged in such a way that it was clear and findable by all our users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical Record Startup</title>
      <link>/portfolio/phrhero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/phrhero/</guid>
      <description>Beta Signup and Branding Phase one of this project involved me creating a recognizable brand, informing users about what the brand does, and then hopefully getting users to sign up for beta
The phrHero branding and identity embodies the values that the company hopes to convey. It wants to rescue it&#39;s users from the complications of personal medical records. This is where the playful hero character came from...
   Educate our audience A well thought-out beta sign-up website helped us to engage our users, while educating them at the same time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Preserver Mobile App Personal Project</title>
      <link>/portfolio/life-preserver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/life-preserver/</guid>
      <description>Onboarding   Web Login / Sign-Up   Helpful and Intuitive Checklist   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spargo Hotel Reservation Dashboard Redesign</title>
      <link>/portfolio/spargo-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/spargo-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Admin Dashboard Home   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>